Not only am I still alive,
ليس فقط أنني لا أزال على قيد الحياة،
I will make you adulterous scoundrels
سأجعلكم أوغادًا زناة
pay the price.
ادفع الثمن.
Son,
ابن،
they say you stole something.
يقولون أنك سرقت شيئاً.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Mom, I didn't.
أمي، لم أفعل.
Your son is blameless before heaven and earth.
ابنك بلا لوم أمام السماء والأرض.
I caught these two committing adultery.
لقد ضبطت هذين الشخصين يرتكبان الزنا.
They tried to kill me to silence me.
لقد حاولوا قتلي لإسكاتي.
Yanzhi,
يانزي،
we've treated you well.
لقد عاملناك بشكل جيد.
Did you lose your conscience?
هل فقدت ضميرك؟
Chen Yuanqi,
تشن يوانكي,
you're twisting the truth.
أنت تحرف الحقيقة.
You were the one who stole the spiritual medicine.
أنت الذي سرق الدواء الروحي.
You even tried to violate me.
حتى أنك حاولت انتهاكي.
I am a traditional woman.
أنا امرأة تقليدية.
How could I endure such humiliation?
كيف أستطيع أن أتحمل مثل هذا الإذلال؟
Luckily, Young Master Fu saved me.
لحسن الحظ، لقد أنقذني السيد الشاب فو.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
I am a woman of virtue.
أنا امرأة فضيلة.
Would I use my own chastity to slander you?
هل أستخدم عفتي لتشويه سمعتك؟
Yanzhi makes sense.
يانزي منطقي.
The Chen family are just poor nobodies.
عائلة تشين مجرد فقراء لا قيمة لهم.
Would Young Master Fu Qingyun ever slander him?
هل سيقوم السيد الشاب فو تشينغ يون بتشويه سمعته على الإطلاق؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Chen Yuanqi,
تشن يوانكي,
you've ruined Yanzhi's reputation.
لقد دمرت سمعة يانزي.
You've tarnished the Fu family's honor.
لقد شوهت شرف عائلة فو.
Today, I will use your and your mother's blood to show everyone
اليوم سأستخدم دمك ودم والدتك لإظهار للجميع
that the Fu family's honor cannot be defiled.
أن شرف عائلة فو لا يمكن تدنيسه.
What evil technique are you practicing?
ما هي التقنية الشريرة التي تمارسها؟
Chen Yuanqi, let go!
تشن يوانكي، اتركه!
My Fu family
عائلتي فو
is the top noble family in Chang'an.
هي العائلة النبيلة العليا في تشانغآن.
If you dare touch me,
إذا تجرأت على لمسي،
the Fu family will surely
عائلة فو سوف تكون بالتأكيد
The noble families of Chang'an
العائلات النبيلة في تشانغآن
can do whatever evil they please?
هل يستطيعون أن يفعلوا الشر الذي يريدونه؟
Act lawlessly?
التصرف بشكل غير قانوني؟
Today,
اليوم،
I will destroy you.
سأدمرك.
I was wrong! I was wrong!
لقد كنت مخطئا! لقد كنت مخطئا!
Stop! Please spare me!
توقف! أرجوك أنقذني!
Fu Qingyun,
فو تشينغيون,
my family has always been honest.
عائلتي كانت دائما صادقة.
Yet you keep pushing us.
ومع ذلك تستمر في دفعنا.
Now someone wants your life,
الآن شخص ما يريد حياتك،
and you beg for mercy.
وتطلب الرحمة.
When you committed all those heartless acts,
عندما ارتكبت كل تلك الأفعال القاسية،
did you ever think this day would come?
هل كنت تتخيل أن هذا اليوم سيأتي؟
Chen Yuanqi,
تشن يوانكي,
I truly know I was wrong.
أنا أعلم حقًا أنني كنت مخطئًا.
Please, let me go.
من فضلك دعني أذهب.
Today,
اليوم،
I will take your miserable life.
سأأخذ حياتك البائسة.
Prepare to die!
استعد للموت!
Son,
ابن،
are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Senior Brother, you're useless.
أخي الأكبر، أنت عديم الفائدة.
A noble family's young master
سيد شاب لعائلة نبيلة
defeated by a mere commoner?
هزم من قبل مجرد شخص عادي؟
How did you end up so pathetic?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر إلى هذا الحد من الشفقة؟
Rumor has it
الاشاعة تتضمن هذا
the top inner disciple of Tianyuan Academy
التلميذ الداخلي الأعلى لأكاديمية تيانيوان
such a brilliant talent
موهبة رائعة كهذه
would appear in our Feiyun Village?
ستظهر في قرية فييون الخاصة بنا؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Lowly commoner,
عامة الناس المتواضعين،
how dare you disrespect the Fu family of Chang'an?
كيف تجرؤ على عدم احترام عائلة فو من تشانغآن؟
Today, your Chen family
اليوم، عائلتك تشين
will be wiped out.
سيتم القضاء عليها.
No,
لا،
my spiritual energy
طاقتي الروحية
is draining so quickly.
يتم استنزافه بسرعة كبيرة.
My Energy-Dispersing Hand makes your energy deplete twice as fast.
يدي التي توزع الطاقة تجعل طاقتك تستنزف أسرع بمرتين.
Chen Yuanqi,
تشن يوانكي,
you probably can't muster any spiritual energy now.
ربما لا تستطيع حشد أي طاقة روحية الآن.
Even without spiritual energy,
حتى بدون الطاقة الروحية،
so what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
You can match me with just your physical strength?
هل يمكنك أن تنافسني بقوتك الجسدية فقط؟
If I don't kill you today,
إذا لم أقتلك اليوم،
you'll become a great threat.
سوف تصبح تهديدًا كبيرًا.
Son
ابن
Mother
الأم
Chen Yuanqi
تشن يوانكي
Take a good look
خذ نظرة جيدة
This is what happens when you offend the Fu family
هذا ما يحدث عندما تسيء لعائلة فو
Let go of my mother
اترك أمي
Mother
الأم
Son
ابن
Don't worry
لا تقلق
You're next
أنت التالي
Mother
الأم
Netherworld evil power
قوة الشر في العالم السفلي
Soul summoning
استدعاء الروح
Soul separation
انفصال الروح
No
لا
Under my control
تحت سيطرتي
Mother
الأم
Senior Sister, slow down.
الأخت الكبرى، أبطئي.
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Senior Sister, slow down.
الأخت الكبرى، أبطئي.
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
Thank you, Senior Sister, for saving my life.
شكرا لك، أختي الكبرى، على إنقاذ حياتي.
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
Of course I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
You are an inner disciple, Senior Sister.
أنت تلميذة داخلية، أختي الكبرى.
The Frost Fairy, Jiang Yumeng.
جنية الصقيع، جيانغ يومينغ.
Tianyuan Academy.
أكاديمية تيانيوان.
Who doesn't admire you?
من لا يعجب بك؟
When I was at the academy before,
عندما كنت في الأكاديمية من قبل،
Senior Sister, Senior Sister!
الأخت الكبرى، الأخت الكبرى!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
This is bad.
هذا سيء.
It's the Energy-Dispersing Hand.
إنها اليد التي توزع الطاقة.
Don't be afraid, Senior Sister.
لا تخافي يا أختي الكبرى.
I'll resolve it for you now.
سأحلها لك الآن.
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
Why are you leaning on me yourself?
لماذا تعتمد علي بنفسك؟
This... this is improper.
هذا...هذا غير لائق.
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
Goddess.
إلهة.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Your qi is pure yang, hers is pure yin.
طاقتك هي يانغ نقية، وطاقتها هي يين نقية.
It's natural for yin and yang to attract.
من الطبيعي أن ينجذب الين واليانج.
You're a grown man, what's wrong with a girl snuggling up to you?
أنت رجل ناضج، ما المشكلة في أن تقترب منك فتاة؟
Are you losing out?
هل أنت خاسر؟
Don't act like some prudish virgin man, alright?
لا تتصرف مثل رجل عذراء متحفظ، حسنًا؟
But I am one.
ولكنني واحد منهم.
Besides,
بجانب،
Senior Sister Jiang saved me.
الأخت الكبرى جيانغ أنقذتني.
How could I take advantage of her?
كيف يمكنني الاستفادة منها؟
No, I can't.
لا، لا أستطيع.
I have to stop channeling my energy right away.
يجب علي أن أتوقف عن توجيه طاقتي على الفور.
If you stop, she'll die instantly.
إذا توقفت، سوف تموت على الفور.
You're worse than a beast.
أنت أسوأ من الوحش.
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.